Suresh Ch



sureshmudiraj563@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/ch-suresh-47a625197



9951942337



https://sureshch97.github.io/myportfolio/

Summary

Developed Product Features from scratch using MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React). Skilled in C, Python, JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and MongoDB.

Specialized in Computer Science Engineering from (VITAE) Vignan Institute Of Technology and Aeronautical Engineering

Experience



Full Stack Engineer

Yours mentor

Dec 2020 - Present (6 months +)

Full Stack Engineer Yours mentor Dec 2020 - Present - Trained in Full Stack Product Development with Yours Mentor company.

-I also developed Projects Using React.js , Node.js and Java Script

Education



Vignan's Institute of Technology & Aeronautical Engineering

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science

2016 - 2020

- -Scored 6.89 CGPA Overall in B.Tech
- -Participated in Ethical Hacking Contest

Nagarjuna junior college

Intermediate, M.P.C

2014 - 2016

-Scored 95% Overall in Intermediate

Zilla Parishad High School

S.S.C

2013 - 2014

- -Scored 8.5 CGPA in acadamics
- -got medals in Sports and Essay writing competion in Independence day celebrations

Licenses & Certifications



MERN Stack Front To Back: Full Stack React, Redux & Node.js - Udemy

UC-ececeb71-d55b-4c48-ac0e-f2d9b43b4d17



Programming Foundations: Web Security - LinkedIn Learning · Course Certificate

Modern java Script From The Beginning - Udemy

UC-e22fdd84-dcbe-474b-aada-f74e9a7d982d

- **ETHICAL HACKING** ROBOSAPIENS TECHNOLOGIES Pvt. Ltd.
- complete java MANAC INFOTECH PRIVATE LIMITED ELT/20190957

Skills

React.js • Node.js • Express.js • MongoDB • Git • JavaScript • Java • HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap